cdkeys.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy | CDkeys.com

The brand name “CDKeys.com” is wholly owned by “Omnyex E Commerce DMCC”, a private company incorporated under the laws of DMCC Free Zone, having its principle place of business at Unit 2603, JBC4, JLT, Dubai, UAE, license number JLT-69058, hereafter referred to as “CDKeys.com”. Omnyex E Commerce DMCC wholly owns Sensible Digital B.V., incorporated under the laws of the Netherlands having its place of business at Stationsplein 45, Rotterdam, 3013 AK, Netherlands which processes payments on behalf Omnyex E Commerce DMCC, depending on the method of payment selected. Payments for USA based customers may be processed by Sensible Digital LLC, a Nevada LLC incorporated under the laws of the State of Nevada, having its principle place of business at Suite 02-189, Two Summerlin, 10845 Griffith Peak Drive, Las Vegas, NV 89135, USA.

This privacy policy sets out how [CDKeys.com](https://www.cdkeys.com/) uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. [CDKeys.com](https://www.cdkeys.com/) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. [CDKeys.com](https://www.cdkeys.com/) may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should therefore check this page regularly to ensure that you are happy with any changes we make.

### What we collect?

We may collect the following information:

  * Your name
  * Your contact information including your email address
  * Your demographic information including preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the complete list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

### What we do with the information we gather?

We gather this information so that we can better understand your needs and provide you with an improved service. In particular, we record information for the following reasons:

  * For our internal record keeping.
  * To improve our products and services.
  * So we can send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. 
  * Finally, to customise the website according to your interests.

### What about Security?

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How do we use cookies?

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes , after which the data is removed from the system.

Cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Many web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. You should note though that this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you’ve used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. We therefore cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and these sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website you are visiting..

### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, keep an eye out for the box that you can click to indicate whether or not you want your information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * If you have previously given us permission to use your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at [mail@cdkeys.com](mailto:mail@cdkeys.com)

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you have given us permission for this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [support@cdkeys.com](mailto:support@cdkeys.com).

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible at [support@cdkeys.com](mailto:support@cdkeys.com). We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

### List of cookies we collect

Want to know what cookies we collect? The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE name| COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | The category info on the page, that allows pages to display more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer ID with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it's allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently participated in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have participated in.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use of cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.
